A few hours later...
What? The Red God?
Yes, he's making strange movements.
He's not moving by himself, is he?
No, he's using a dead body as a means of communication.
However, the contact between the White Beard and the Red God is too dangerous!
Yes, that's true.
However, the Red God is not a man who can do anything but rampage.
He's not the kind of man who can decide what to do with the world by himself.
He's just looking at how poorly he's moving.
More importantly, we're in the Seventh World now.
We have to hurry to confirm Crocodile's identity.
Don't underestimate even a single hole.
The three great forces of the Humanity will directly put a crack in the world.
We have to protect it.
That's why we're calling on the Seventh World.
I wonder how many of them will show up.
After all, they're pirates. They're selfish.
Crocodile...
You've done something troublesome.
I can't let this man, who took it, go.
Monkey D. Luffy...